<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Personal site of Peter White</title>
    <link>https://peterwhite.pw/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Personal site of Peter White</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ie</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 18:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://peterwhite.pw/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/new-zealand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/new-zealand/</guid>
      <description>So 2020 has arrived and it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since the last post, oh well! While I was in the area, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go without seeing New Zealand. I flew into Christchurch and immediately the friendliness of the NZ people greeted me with a free beer at the hostel I stayed in. I didn&amp;rsquo;t stay too long in Christchurch, and ventured down towards Queenstown, stopping off at Lake Pukaki on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Part 3</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Oops, guess it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I was supposed to do Australia Part 3. In my defence, I was having fun travelling and didn&amp;rsquo;t think to blog. I&amp;rsquo;ll get around to the rest of my posts about my trip soon, especially now that I&amp;rsquo;ve returned back to Ireland.&#xA;After leaving Sydney, I flew southward to Melbourne, the food capital of Australia with an extraordinary amount of coffee shops. Sadly that was lost on me, being only a tea drinker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Part 2</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 06:54:50 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-2/</guid>
      <description>After experiencing Brisbane and Gold Coast, it was time to move southwards to Sydney. I&amp;rsquo;d say that this was probably my favourite part of Australia, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty to do as a tourist, although I&amp;rsquo;d hate to live in Sydney due to how much of a nightmare the commute would be. The hostel I was staying at was also good craic, with plenty of fun and interesting people, so it was never a quiet time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Part 1</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 15:02:39 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Quite a bit of time since the last update. I wish I could say I was backpacking with no internet, but unfortunately, after a bad experience in India, I decided to pause my travels for a while, mainly sticking to Europe for a few months. After a bit of soul-searching, I kicked off my travels again with Australia in January, deciding to leave Asia for the future. I&amp;rsquo;m already finished with Australia, so this series of posts will just go over my experience there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adventure Has a Rocky Start</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/an-adventure-has-a-rocky-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 15:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/an-adventure-has-a-rocky-start/</guid>
      <description>The adventure has well and truly started now. I&amp;rsquo;ve left behind Europe and all its conveniences and arrived in India on the 26th. It&amp;rsquo;s certainly &amp;hellip; different to what I imagined India would be like. The best way I can describe it is barely controlled chaos. Of course, that may just be Delhi, being home to around 18 million people, chaos should be expected.&#xA;After spending a month in Germany and getting used to following &amp;ldquo;the rules&amp;rdquo;, it&amp;rsquo;s quite a culture shock to come to Delhi where the rules are way more lax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adventure Begins</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/an-adventure-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 14:25:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/an-adventure-begins/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m begining to fulfill one of my dreams in life, and have started a round-the-world trip for the guts of a year. I quit my job at the end of July, and have begun my trip in Barcelona, Spain with one of my friends. The rest of the trip, however, will mostly be on my own, with the occasional stop-off to friends/family abroad. I do have a small travelling companion, who goes by the name of Herr Quack (since I got him in Germany).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
