<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Australia on Personal site of Peter White</title>
    <link>https://peterwhite.pw/tags/australia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Australia on Personal site of Peter White</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ie</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:15:37 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://peterwhite.pw/tags/australia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Australia Part 3</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Oops, guess it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I was supposed to do Australia Part 3. In my defence, I was having fun travelling and didn&amp;rsquo;t think to blog. I&amp;rsquo;ll get around to the rest of my posts about my trip soon, especially now that I&amp;rsquo;ve returned back to Ireland.&#xA;After leaving Sydney, I flew southward to Melbourne, the food capital of Australia with an extraordinary amount of coffee shops. Sadly that was lost on me, being only a tea drinker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Part 2</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 06:54:50 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-2/</guid>
      <description>After experiencing Brisbane and Gold Coast, it was time to move southwards to Sydney. I&amp;rsquo;d say that this was probably my favourite part of Australia, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty to do as a tourist, although I&amp;rsquo;d hate to live in Sydney due to how much of a nightmare the commute would be. The hostel I was staying at was also good craic, with plenty of fun and interesting people, so it was never a quiet time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Part 1</title>
      <link>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 15:02:39 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://peterwhite.pw/post/australia-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Quite a bit of time since the last update. I wish I could say I was backpacking with no internet, but unfortunately, after a bad experience in India, I decided to pause my travels for a while, mainly sticking to Europe for a few months. After a bit of soul-searching, I kicked off my travels again with Australia in January, deciding to leave Asia for the future. I&amp;rsquo;m already finished with Australia, so this series of posts will just go over my experience there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
